A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1985 (Accession 37778)., Extent: x cubic feet (x boxes)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Lieutenant Governor, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Longwood College, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Marine Resources Commission, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Marine Science, Virginia Institute of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Minority Business Enterprise, Office of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Motor Vehicles, Division of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Norfolk State College, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Old Dominion University, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Outdoor Recreation, Commission on, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Personal Service Funds, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: DPB, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: DPB - Personnel, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: DPB - Policies and procedures, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Policy Guidance Memoranda, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Printing and Duplication - State operations analysis of cost, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Product Commissions (Commerce and Resources), 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Property Records and Insurance, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Public Safety, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Purchases and Supply, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Taxation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Taxation, Dept. of - Legislative Studies, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Taxation, Dept. of - Tax Foundations, Inc., 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Transportation, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Treasury, Dept. of the, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Treasury, Dept. of the - General Fund investment yield, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: University of Virginia, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Economic Review, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS), 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Municipal League, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Administrative Accounting System, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Audit Committee, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Bank of New York, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Board of Trustees, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Investment Committee, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Investment Reports, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Legislation, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Massachusetts Company, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Meetings, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Meidinger and Associates, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Minutes, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Study Commission, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - The Boston Company, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Virginia Bond Portfolio, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Virginia Stock Portfolio, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Volunteerism, Div. of, 1979. (Box 60)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Washington Liaison Office, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Washington National Airport, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: William and Mary, College of, 1979. (Box 61)
  - Directives from the Secretary of Administration and Finance - Exceptions, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Directives from the Dept. of General Services - Issued to state agencies, 1979-1980. (Box 62)
  - Elections, State Board of, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Division of Motor Vehicles, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Education, State Board of, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Emergency and Energy Services, Dept. of, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Employee Position Report, 1979. (Box 62)
  - Employee Position Report, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Office of, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia - Centralization, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia - Recommendations, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Energy Conservation, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Energy Conservation - Coal conversion, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Energy Conservation - Mileage, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Energy Plan, State, 1980. (Box 62)
  - Gasoline tax, 1980. (Box 62)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1980. (Box 62)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1980. (Box 63)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Confederate Memorial Chapel, 1980. (Box 63)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Div. of Engineering and Buildings - Office space, 1980. (Box 63)
  - General Services, Dept. of - 14th Street Tower, 1980. (Box 63)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Study on parking, fees, etc., 1980. (Box 63)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Surplus Property / Land Management, 1980. (Box 63)
  - George Mason University, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor Dalton, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Office - Edwards, Paul G., 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Office - Manson, Jennifer Joy, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Office - Miscellaneous, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Office - Murphy, L.E., 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Office - Press releases and news conferences, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Governor's Roundtable meeting, 1980. (Box 63)
  - Green Springs property, 1980. (Box 63)